https://www.themusiccellar.co.uk/privacy-policy

Products
InstrumentsAlto SaxophoneBanjo & UkeleleBaritoneBaritone SaxophoneBouzoukisCelloClarinetCornetDigital PianoDouble BassEuphoniumFlugel HornFluteFrench HornGuitarHarmonicaKeyboardMandolinMiscellaneousOboePercussionPianoPiccoloRecorderSax Alto/TenorSoprano SaxophoneTenor HornTenor SaxophoneTromboneTrumpetTubaUkuleleViolaViolinAccessoriesAlto SaxophoneBanjo & UkeleleBaritoneBaritone SaxophoneBassoonCelloClarinetCor AnglaisCornetDigital PianoDouble BassDrum&PercussionEuphoniumFlugel HornFluteFrench HornGuitarKeyboardMandolinMicrophonesMiscellaneousMusic TechologyMusical GiftsOboePercussionPiccoloSax Alto/TenorSoprano SaxophoneSousaphoneTenor HornTenor SaxophoneTromboneTrumpetTubaUkuleleViolaViolinMusicAlto SaxophoneBanjo & UkeleleBaritoneBassoonBrass BandCD'sCelloChristmasClarinetCornetDouble BassDrum&PercussionEducational MusicEnsemble MusicEuphoniumFluteFrench HornGuitarKeyboardMandolinMini ScoresMiscellaneousOboeOrganPianoPiano Vocal GuitarRecorderSax Alto/TenorTenor HornTenor SaxophoneTextbookTheoryTromboneTrumpetTubaUkuleleViolaViolinVocal MusicCDs etcCDs Information
About Us
Complaints and Compliments
Assisted Instrument Purchase Scheme A.I.P.S
Rentals
Returns & Warranty
Repairs
Links
Shipping & Delivery
Terms & Conditions
Cookie Information
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Site Map
Privacy Policy
This policy covers the use of personal information collected when you use this site.
From time to time, you may be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name and email address) in order to receive or use services on our website. By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable us to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. When using your personal information we will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.
The site uses sessions to track a user being logged in. Once the user logs in the server identifies the IP address of the user, the site can then identify the user to allow them to see the restricted areas. The session will timeout after a period of no activity or the browser window is closed or the logout button is pressed. No personal information is contained in the session, so it's very secure.
In general, any information you provide will only be used by The Music Cellar and by its agents. Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged by law.
We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
© 2010 The Music Cellar
